Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Marketing, 1975-1999; VIII.
  - General Marketing files, 1975-1999; 1.
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership Sparkle Season and First Night, 1994 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Employees Activities Association, 1996-1997 (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh entertainment market research by the Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1997 (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Federation for Events and Promotions, 1997 (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Filmmakers, 1998 (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Penguins, July 1996 (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette media kit, 1994 (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Radio Organization, April 1996 (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Renaissance News, 1994 (Box 241, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1997-1998 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra ticket design, 1996-1997 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Postage machine at Wood Street Galleries manual, October 1994 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - La Primo Espresso, 1996-1997 (Box 242, Folder 4-5)
    - La Primo Espresso opening photographs, October 1996 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Promotional materials that are included with mailed tickets, 1993-1996 (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Public art project local artists, 1994-1996 (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations Society Pittsburgh Chapter membership directory, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - Puppetry marketing strategies, 1996 (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Report on the Pittsburgh Audience for Theatre Yes, May 1975 (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - Seventh Street Grille, 1995 (Box 242, Folder 12)
    - Shared mailing list, 1994-1995 (Box 242, Folder 13)
    - Sizzling Summer, 1997 (Box 242, Folder 14)
    - Sizzling Summer newspaper clippings and tear sheets, 1997 (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - Spectacular Youth Celebration, May 1999 (Box 242, Folder 16)
    - Sprint PCS sponsorship, 1996-1997 (Box 242, Folder 17)
    - Summer film series, 1997 (Box 242, Folder 18)
    - Summer film series press release with photographs, 1997 (Box 242, Folder 19)
    - Summer film series receipts, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Summer film series settlement, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Summer film series tear sheets, 1997 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Summer film series WQED, July 1997 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Summer film series calendar, 1998 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Summer film series with photographs, 1998 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Ten year financial summary revised layout, May 1995 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Theatre promotional materials (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Theatre restorations and openings articles and newspaper clippings, 1981-1987 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Theatre trolley, 1999 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Third party rental information, May 1995 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Ticket fonts, 1995 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Ticket stock and mailing timelines, 1995-1996 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Ticketing and patron information system needs analysis, 1990 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - TIX closing, September 1993 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - TIX for teachers program, 1997 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - TIX information, 1987-1993 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - TIX moving with photographs, May 1992 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Trust Talk, 1992-1999 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - USAir Magazine advertising, 1995 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - Update calendar and job openings, 1993-1994 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Variety advertisements, 1997-1998 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - WAMO fiftieth anniversary commemorative booklet, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - WPTT, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - WQED underwriting proposals, 1996-1997 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - WTAE Arts Minute, September 1993 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - WTAE Arts Minute general correspondence, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - WTAE Arts Minute surveys, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - WXDX, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - WYEP, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Washington PR Successful Techniques (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Washington Printing and Publishing, 1995 (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - Wasser office approvals, 1996-1997 (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Wood Street Galleries Art in America, September 1996 (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Wood Street Galleries Alfred DeCredico, January 1994 (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Wood Street Galleries David Humphrey, 1995-1996 (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Wood Street Galleries Hard Choices III, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Wood Street Galleries International Survey of Glass, September 1994 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Wood Street Galleries Ken Ferguson, 1995 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Wood Street Galleries Ken Ferguson, 1995 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Wood Street Galleries Lecture series, April 1997 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Wood Street Galleries opening, 1992 (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Wood Street Galleries opening press release, January 1992 (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Wood Street Galleries promotional materials (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Wood Street Galleries Red Grooms exhibit, March 1995 (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Wood Street Galleries Red Grooms survey, 1995 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Wood Street Galleries Robert Cumming, January 1995 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Wood Street Galleries Studio Museum of Harlem, September 1994 (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Wood Street Galleries WYEP, May 1997 (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Wood Street Galleries Xu Bing, July 1998 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Y Not? centenary celebration, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Youth Film Festival, 1993-1996 (Box 246, Folder 13-15)
    - Youth Film Festival Allerton Marketing Communications Inc, August 1995 (Box 246, Folder 16)
    - Youth Film Festival marketing, 1995 (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1989-1995; 2.
    The newspaper clippings are arranged in two groups. First are clippings that were primarily assembled by a press clipping service. The second group are clippings that were specifically assembled to be distributed during the bi-monthly board meetings of the Cultural Trust.
    - Newspaper clippings, March 1989 - September 1990 (Box 247, Folder 1-19)
    - Newspaper clippings, October 1990 - September 1991 (Box 248, Folder 1-13)
    - Newspaper clippings, September - December 1991 (Box 248, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings, October 1991 - May 1993 (Box 249, Folder 1-22)
    - Newspaper clippings, June 1993 - January 1994 (Box 250, Folder 1-11)
    - Newspaper clippings, January 1994 - August 1994 (Box 251, Folder 1-11)
    - Newspaper clippings, August - September 1994 (Box 251, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings, September - December 1994 (Box 252, Folder 1-5)
    - Newspaper clippings, January - February 1995 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings, March - August 1995 (Box 253, Folder 1-6)
    - Newspaper clippings, September - November 1995 (Box 254, Folder 1-2)
    - Cultural Trust board meeting newspaper clippings, July 1990 - March 1991 (Box 255, Folder 1-5)
    - Cultural Trust board meeting death of Senator John Heinz newspaper clippings, April - May 1991 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Trust board meeting newspaper clippings, May 1991 - September 1994 (Box 255, Folder 7-22)
  - Arts Blastoff and Live on Stage files, 1993-1999; 3.
    Arts Blastoff was the original name for the Cultural Trust's programming series designed for children. The series changed its title to Live on Stage before it's second season. Each season has files on advertising, promotions, subscription information, ticket sales, etc. These files are in chronological order by season and then alphabetical by folder subject.
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season, 1993-1994 (Box 256, Folder 1-3)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season advertising, 1993-1994 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 93-94 season event set-up form (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season marketing, 1993-1994 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season membership package, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season promotional materials, 1993-1994 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season survey, 1994 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 season telemarketing, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Arts Blastoff 93-94 and 94-95 seasons sponsorship, 1993-1994 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season advertising, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 3-4)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season Allegheny County allocation, November 1994 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season brochure, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Arts Blastoff 94-95 season budget, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Arts Blastoff 94-95 season budget re-projections, 1993-1994 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season community services, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season contracts, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season family programs, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season final settlements, October 1994 (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season grant application, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season income and expenses, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season marketing, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season marketing, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season marketing and membership revenue, 1994-1995 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season marketing and pr plan, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season marketing and pr plan revised, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season media sponsorship, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season membership winners, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season Mid-Atlantic Arts Foundation Grant Award, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season overview, February 1995 (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season payments, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season photographs (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season planning education advisory committee, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 12-13)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season settlement reports, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season sponsorship, 1994 (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season staff meeting, September 1994 (Box 258, Folder 16)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season study guides (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season technical sheets, April 1994 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season ticket holds, 1994 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season ticket orders, September 1994 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 season ticket reports, 1994-1995 (Box 259, Folder 5-6)
    - Live on Stage 94-95 and 95-96 seasons Girl Scouts, 1994-1995 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season, 1995-1996 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season, 1995-1996 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season announcement news release, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season Bayer reports, 1995-1996 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season brochure, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season combined promotion of Tragedy of Macbeth and Boys Choir of Harlem, October 1995 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season expenses, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season final report, 1996 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season grants, 1995-1996 (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season member mailing, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season photographs to duplicate, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season ticket reports, 1995 (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Live on Stage 95-96 season ticket reports, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season, 1996-1997 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season advertising and public relations recap, June 1997 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season Bayer Corporation, November 1996 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season brochure, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 5-6)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season development, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season letters for members, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season letters for subscribers, 1996-1997 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season marketing, 1996-1997 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season membership cards, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season patron study, April 1997 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season planning calendar, April 1997 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season program advertising rates, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season subscription guide, September 1996 (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season subscription pack, September 1996 (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season subscriptions and expenses, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - Live on Stage 96-97 season ticket pricing, 1996 (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season, 1996-1998 (Box 262, Folder 1-3)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season Bayer Corporation, July 1997 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season brochure, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season contracts, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season corporate flyers, 1997-1998 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season dining guide, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season expenses, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season letters, 1997-1998 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season preliminary information, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season receipts, 1997 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season study guides (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season tear sheets, 1997-1998 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Live on Stage 97-98 season ticket reports, 1997-1998 (Box 262, Folder 15)
    - Live on Stage 98-99 season, 1995-1998 (Box 263, Folder 1-2)
    - Live on Stage 98-99 season ticket holds, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Live on Stage 99-00 season, 1998-1999 (Box 263, Folder 4-5)
  - Pittsburgh Broadway Series files, 1989-1999; 4.
    The Pittsburgh Broadway Series is the program that brings the national tours of Broadway productions to Pittsburgh. The performances are either held at the Benedum Center or Heinz Hall. The 1989/1990 season through the 1999/2000 season is covered. Each season has folders containing some of the following topics – expenses, marketing, advertising, group sales, subscriptions, brochure design, sponsorship, pricing, etc. The materials are arranged in chronological order by season and then alphabetically by folder subject.
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 89-90 season, 1989 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 89-90 season related expenses, 1989 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 90-91 season expenses, 1990 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 91-92 season expenses, 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season marketing, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 92-93 season Phantom of the Opera review, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 93-94 season, 1993 (Box 265, Folder 4-5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 93-94 season amortization, 1993 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 93-94 season opening nights, 1993 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 94-95 season amortization, 1994 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 95-96 season, 1995 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 95-96 season advertising, 1995 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 95-96 season marketing settlements, 1995-1996 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 95-96 season opening nights (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season, 1995-1996 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season, 1991-1997 (Box 267, Folder 1-3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season correspondence, 1996 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season Fluted Mushroom, July 1996 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season group sales, 1995-1997 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season group sales brochure, 1996 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season group sales leads, 1996 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season holds (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season KDKA, 1996-1997 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season marketing, 1995-1996 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season marketing plan, 1996-1997 (Box 268, Folder 2-3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season MasterCard, 1996-1997 (Box 268, Folder 4-5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season new acquisition advertising, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season opening nights, 1996-1997 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season PACE booking advisory, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season press release, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season pricing, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season pricing matrix, 1996-1997 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season poster and flyer distribution, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season la Prima Espresso, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season program advertising, March 1996 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season renewal envelopes, March 1996 (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season renewal forms, March 1996 (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season restaurant information, 1996 (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season settlements, 1997 (Box 268, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season Sprint PCS, 1996-1997 (Box 268, Folder 19-20)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season subscription book and restaurant coupons, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season subscription campaign, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season subscription expenses, 1996-1997 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season subscription package, 1995-1996 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season subscription price controversy, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season tear sheets, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season ticket problems, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season timeline, 1995-1996 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season turnpike brochures, 1996 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season William Penn, August 1996 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season WJAS marketing plan, August 1996 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season WPXI, 1996 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 96-97 season WTAE, 1996 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season, 1997-1998 (Box 270, Folder 5-7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season advisories, 1997-1998 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season amortization, 1997 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season brochure, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 1-2)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season card, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season group sales, 1997-1998 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season handouts and postcards, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season KDKA, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season letterhead, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season logos (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season marketing and advertising, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season MasterCard, April 1997 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season new acquisitions, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season new acquisitions stuffer, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season PACE booking advisories, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season press conference, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season prices, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season production photos (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season promotions for Phantom of the Opera and Rent, 1996-1997 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season proposals, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season renew postcard, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season renewals, 1997-1998 (Box 271, Folder 20-22)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season samples (Box 271, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season sponsors, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season subscription, 1996-1997 (Box 271, Folder 25)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season survey, 1997-1998 (Box 271, Folder 26)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season ticket stock, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 27)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 97-98 season timeline, 1997 (Box 271, Folder 28)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season, 1997-1999 (Box 272, Folder 1-4)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season advertising, 1998-1999 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season advertising settlements, 1998-1999 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season brochure quotes, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season contracts, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season Geyer Printing Company quotes, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season group sales brochure, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season insertions, July 1998 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season mailing forms, 1997-1998 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season marketing, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season restaurants, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season samples (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season schedule, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 98-99 season ticket stock, 1998 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Broadway Series 99-00 season, 1998-1999 (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Street Fair files, 1994-1999; 5.
    The Cultural Trust's Street Fair began in 1995 and became an annual late summer early autumn downtown event. The files are in chronological order by year and then alphabetical by subject.
    - Street Fair 1995 (Box 273, Folder 1-2)